<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache Superset :: Documentation At Your Wish</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/index.html</link>
    <description>A Modern Data Exploration and Visualization Platform Warning&#xD;Please note this is not Official documentation and prepared as I am exploring these tools. If you see any issue or any missing content please feel free to correct and create a pull request or you can reach to me on contact@shantanukhond.me. Thank you!&#xD;Apache Superset is an open-source business intelligence and data visualization platform. It empowers users to explore, visualize, and share insights from their data, providing a user-friendly interface for crafting compelling dashboards and reports.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Methods to setup Apache Superset To setup apache superset there are multiple ways. Please select appropriate way to set up from below&#xA;Docker based installation This includes installation of superset on docker container using docker compose. To run as it is you will need docker installed. If you want to customize docker image then you must have a strong compute with at-least 16GB of ram to build UI using npm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/upgrading/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/upgrading/index.html</guid>
      <description>Upgrading superset to latest version To upgrade superset please select the installation type you have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/customization/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/customization/index.html</guid>
      <description>Superset Customization We will be configuring the following (more will be added as I explore):&#xA;Superset Customization Setting Up App Name Setting Up Logo Setting Up Favicon Icon Changing Loading GIF Setting Up Custom Color Theme Setting Up App Name Setting up the app name is easy and can be done by adding the following constant in the superset_config.py file:&#xA;APP_NAME = &#34;My Reporting Application&#34;Setting Up Logo To change the logo, place your logo in the /app/superset/superset_env/lib/python3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/configuration/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/configuration/index.html</guid>
      <description>Configuring chromium for superset To be used for Alerts &amp; Reports, Thumbnails, etc. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/embedding/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/embedding/index.html</guid>
      <description>Installing Apache Superset </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alerts and Reports</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/alerts-and-reports/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/alerts-and-reports/index.html</guid>
      <description>Alerts and Reports With Superset Note&#xD;Chromium headless or firefox is necessary to get alerts and reports running as expected as well Celery Redis Should be installed and configured. We have documentation you can refer to [Chromium Configuration] and [apache-superset/configuration/celery-workers--beat/] Thank you!&#xD;To get Alerts and reports working. We need SMTP creds, and chrome or firefox should be installed. For this tutorial I am using chrome.&#xA;In Superset Config file i.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautifying Visuals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/beautifying-visuals/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/beautifying-visuals/index.html</guid>
      <description>Beautifying Apache Superset Visuals Such as Card visual, table etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running in Dev Mode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/custom-visuals/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/custom-visuals/index.html</guid>
      <description>Running Apache Superset in Development Mode As we want to customize apache superset and or to develop custom visuals we first need to run Apache Superset in development mode to quickly see the changes and modify the code.&#xA;Clone the Apache Superset We first need to clone the apache superset let do that first. I am still going to use 4.0&#xA;git clone --depth=1 -b 4.0 https://github.com/apache/superset.gitMove inside Superset directory</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>