<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation :: Documentation At Your Wish</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/index.html</link>
    <description>Methods to setup Apache Superset To setup apache superset there are multiple ways. Please select appropriate way to set up from below&#xA;Docker based installation This includes installation of superset on docker container using docker compose. To run as it is you will need docker installed. If you want to customize docker image then you must have a strong compute with at-least 16GB of ram to build UI using npm.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/docker/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/docker/index.html</guid>
      <description>Creating and deploying Apache Superset’s customized docker image Youtube Video To Follow Steps For youtube To create custom docker image lets clone superset’s github Repo using following command. To reduce time and resources we will only clone till depth 1 and for this tutorial I am selecting 4.0 branch.&#xA;git clone --depth=1 -b 4.0 https://github.com/apache/superset.git Let’s move to directory&#xA;cd superset Create a dir I am calling it to_be_copied and create following directory structure in it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PiPy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/pipy/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/pipy/index.html</guid>
      <description>SUPERSET PRODUCTION INSTALLATION Set up environment Update Ubuntu/Debian sudo apt update -y &amp; sudo apt upgrade -y Install dependencies sudo apt-get install build-essential libssl-dev libffi-dev python3-dev python3-pip libsasl2-dev libldap2-dev default-libmysqlclient-dev python3.10-venv Create app directory for superset and dependencies sudo mkdir /app&#xD;sudo chown user /app&#xD;cd /app Create python environment mkdir superset&#xD;cd superset&#xD;python3 -m venv superset_env&#xD;. superset_env/bin/activate&#xD;pip install --upgrade setuptools pip Install Required dependencies pip install pillow&#xD;pip install apache-superset Create superset config file and set environment variable touch superset_config.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSL For windows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/wsl/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apache-superset/installation/wsl/index.html</guid>
      <description>Installing Apache Superset Youtube Video To Follow Once WSL is installed please follow steps written in PiPy installation documentation</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>